getsongbird.com 2013-10-06

# Songbird

## Pioneers of the Inevitable, Inc.

Privacy Policy

* * *

1\. Introduction. 

We are committed to handling information in a secure and responsible manner so that users may confidently enjoy a personalized experience through our websites and services. This privacy policy applies to all websites and services operated by Pioneers of the Inevitable, Inc. (“POTI”), including http://getsongbird.com/, and any applications made available by POTI. This policy describes information that POTI receives, gathers, manages, analyzes, and transfers and how POTI uses that information to bring you its websites and services. If you have questions or concerns about how POTI uses information, you may contact us by mail at Pioneers of the Inevitable, Inc., Privacy, PO BOX 322, San Francisco, CA 94114 or by email at privacy@songbirdnest.com 

2\. Use of Information. 

Like all website and web service operators, POTI receives, gathers, manages, analyzes, and transfers information. POTI does so in order to operate and maintain its current websites and services as well as its future innovative offerings. For example, POTI may receive, gather, manage, analyze, and transfer: 

  * non-personally identifying information such as browser type, location, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of use of its websites and services;
  * information that it receives from third parties (for example, Facebook) or that its users have themselves provided to POTI or made public;
  * information in order to correspond with users;
  * information concerning the habits of its users when using POTI websites and services, for example, information about a user’s collecting, commenting, listening, skipping, and sharing;
  * information in order to display advertising about goods and services that may be of interest to users; and
  * information to third parties that these parties may use for their own purposes.

3\. Non-Disclosure of Certain Personally-Identifying Information. 

Some users of POTI websites and services provide us with personally-identifying information when registering to use our websites and services or when entering into transactions with us concerning paid-for products and services. For example, a user may provide us with an email address in order to register for access to a free or paid-for web service or may provide us with a physical mailing address when purchasing a product or service. Unless a user provides POTI with permission at the time of disclosure or at another time, POTI will not transfer personally-identifying information collected at the time of registration or a commercial transaction except as follows. POTI may disclose such personally-identifying information to those of its employees, contractors, partners, and affiliated organizations that need to know that information in order to process it on POTI’s behalf or to assist in the provision of POTI websites and services and that have agreed to not disclose it to others. POTI may disclose such information in response to a subpoena, court order, or other governmental request, or when POTI believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights or interests of POTI, third parties, or the public at large. 

4\. Public Information. 

POTI may ask a user to provide it with a username to be used on its websites and services. Users may be asked to create user profiles within POTI websites and services. Usernames and profiles will be made available to the public. Users may choose to use POTI websites and services to make information public, for example, a user may use a POTI application to distribute information about himself or herself on a social network such as Facebook or Twitter. POTI cannot control how information is used and further disseminated by these social networks. POTI endeavors to give its users control over the distribution of information through its websites and services. 

5\. Information from Third Parties. 

POTI may obtain from third parties information about users and the use of POTI websites and services by users. For example, a user may choose to use a POTI web service or web application upon a third party social network platform such as Facebook and to allow POTI to access personally-identifying and non-personally-identifying information gathered by such social network (for example, from Facebook, the user’s email address, user’s “likes,” and friend’s “likes”). POTI may combine such accessed information with other information and use it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

6\. Cross-Border Transfers. 

POTI facilities and third parties with whom POTI shares information may obtain or process information outside of the country in which POTI originally received such information. As a result, use or disclosure of information may require transfer of that information to a country that mandates a lesser level of data protection than a user’s home country. 

7\. Security. 

POTI undertakes a range of security measures including physical access restraints, technical security monitoring, and internal security reviews of the environment to help protect information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, and destruction. 

8\. Other Sites and Services. 

POTI websites and services may link to websites and services offered by third parties who maintain separate privacy policies. POTI web applications may interact with third party social network platforms such as Facebook. POTI suggests that its users read and understand the privacy policy of each party with whom the user engages. 

9\. Children. 

Children under the age of 13 may not use POTI websites or services. If it comes to our attention that we have collected personally-identifying information from any person under the age of 13, we will endeavor to delete this information as soon as possible. Children between the ages of 13 and 17 should use POTI websites and services only with parental consent. 

10\. Access to Information. 

Users may request access, correction, or deletion of personally-identifying information as required by law. POTI will seek to comply with any such request. Requests may be made to POTI at the addresses mentioned above. 

11\. Cookies and Web Beacons. 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s device and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. POTI uses cookies to help POTI identify and track visitors, their usage, and their access preferences. Users who do not wish to have cookies placed on their devices should set their browser to refuse cookies before using POTI websites and services, with the drawback that certain features of POTI websites and services may not function properly without the aid of cookies. If user does not enable cookies and or web beacons, POTI has no obligation to ensure proper functionality of POTI websites and or services. POTI websites and services may include advertisements and other content delivered by advertisers and other third parties. This privacy policy does not cover cookies set by any such parties. A web beacon is a small (often invisible) graphic image or other web programming code embedded in a web page or email. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used by POTI for a number of purposes, including to count visitors to POTI websites and services, to monitor how users navigate POTI services, and to count how many sent email messages are actually opened. 

12\. Business Transfers. 

If POTI is acquired or sells all or a portion of its assets to another company, or declares bankruptcy, it is likely that information held by POTI will be transferred away from POTI. 

13\. Change of Policy. 

POTI may change its Privacy Policy from time to time. Your use of a POTI website or services after a change means that you accept the changed policy. Users should check this page to review any changes. POTI will endeavor to notify all registered users of changes to this policy.
